Chen Hui!
I've been with you all this time.
Just tell me the truth.
Are you a murderer or not?
A murderer?
Chen Hui is a murderer!
Hurry up and leave!
Chen Hui!
Let me tell you!
If you're a man, get out here!
I want to see for myself
whether you really deserve my Qibao.
Shut up!
Don't be afraid.
A real man
never backs down from a fight.
Listen to me!
If you're a man, come out!
And face me in a fight!
Qibao.
I like you.
I don't care who's in your heart now.
I'll compete with him fair and square.
I won't let him toy with your feelings again.
Let's keep him here for now.
And wait for Captain Chu to back us up.
Okay.
Chen Hui!
Still not coming out, huh?
Won't come out? Fine.
Then I'm coming in to find you!
Wait for me!
Chen Hui!
Wait.
Something feels off.
Stop right there!
Stop!
Over here!
Don't move!
Looks like he planned his escape route.
Split up and chase!
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Police business.
Chen Hui!
Don't move!
Go, now!
Move it!
Chen Hui!
If you've got guts, don't run!
If you're a real man,
come fight me face to face!
He's serious!
Run! Run!
Run!
Chen Hui!
Xiao Jun, get in the car!
Don't move!
Let him go!
Let go!
Watch him.
Are you hurt?
No.
Call for backup.
Tianfang.
Are you okay?
Am I okay?
They almost shot me dead!
Tell me the truth.
Who the hell is Chen Hui?
Knowing too much
won't do you any good.
At a time like this,
how can you still cover for him?
He's a criminal.
And he's got a gun!
Can you wake up?
As long as you're safe.
Wait...
The unattainable is always restless,
the favored take it all for granted.
Hey, wait.
Qibao!
Wait for me!
Captain Chu.
He must've run this way.
They went inside.
Qin Mo.
Before you can stop a crime,
you have to stay alive.
But the man who killed my dad is in there!
Qin Mo.
Before, we didn't know who the suspect was.
Now we're sure.
Chen Hui is Chen Dahui.
Per the recusal rule,
you have to step off the case.
But we're about to catch him!
But once you're involved,
all the evidence could potentially
become inadmissible.
You have to withdraw.
Backup officers are on their way.
They'll take over from you.
Two hundred thousand,
just to get a bag back.
But what can ever
win back Qiqi's heart?
I don't like it when Boss Bai controls me.
When she does, she's like a tyrant.
Everything has to be her way.
But I'm also afraid she'll ignore me,
afraid she doesn't love me.
This conflict has been tormenting me.
I met a man,
and he said,
if a person isn't seen,
they're no different
from being dead.
The reason I act out with Boss Bai,
all the drama,
is because I want her to see me.
Hello?
Got the money ready?
You con artist!
My daughter was never in your hands!
Two hundred thousand wasn't enough for you?
You dare call me again?
Go to hell!
Your daughter may be safe,
but I still have something of hers.
You.
Who are you?
What have you done to my daughter?
I love your daughter very much.
She's right here beside me.
I know everything about you.
Don't try anything funny.
Or I'll take all of your daughter's
private secrets and leak them all.
Don't.
Stay calm.
Please don't.
Next time, either bring money,
or bring Wang Kechen's inheritance.
Reporting in.
Chief.
Captain.
We've already searched this area.
Nothing was found.
Expand the search radius.
Form a dragnet and advance.
Focus on checking footprints.
Signal immediately if anything's off.
We can't let the fugitives slip away.
Yes, sir.
Sun Bo.
Make sure to check
places easy to hide in.
Abandoned houses, basements.
Understood.
Stay safe.
Qin Mo,
don't be too anxious.
Recusal isn't about distrust.
It's the firmest safeguard
of procedural justice.
Your stepping back for now
is to help
the truth better come to light.
Don't worry, Chief.
I'll choose another way
to keep fighting.
Good.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I just can't accept it.
A lot of the time,
it's just like playing chess.
Before you've won,
we all have to be patient.
If you were Chen Hui,
what would you do next?
I don't think he'll stop.
No matter where he is,
we will find him.
Come on.
I'll take you back.
We've been running all night.
I'm exhausted.
This place is good.
No one should come here.
Xiao Jun.
With a murder on our hands, there's no going back.
I've dragged you into this.
Brother Hui.
My old man always called me a born bad seed.
I just take down whoever crosses me.
We're cut from the same cloth.
From now on, we live it up while we can.
The first piece isn't even on the board.
It's way too early to call the game.
Hello.
Hello?
Are you ready?
It's time we met.
Boss.
Are you heading out?
I'd like to treat you and Qibao
to a meal,
to celebrate
our great hero Yu Tianfang's
highly successful rescue mission.
Do you have time?
Yu Tianfang,
let me ask you.
If a man deceived
a woman's heart and body,
and then abandoned her,
what should this woman
do
to punish that man?
Boss,
I... I'm not that kind of man.
A guy like me,
a loyal and devoted good man,
compared to those scumbags out there,
it's the difference between a saint and a wild boar.
I'm not talking about you.
Just tell me,
how do I get back at this scumbag?
Well, with a scumbag,
if it's just a romantic dispute,
with no physical harm
or financial disputes involved,
then I'm afraid
the law can't do anything either.
For these so-called scumbags,
basically, all you've got is moral judgment.
Boss,
what's wrong?
It's unfair.
This is unfair.
Good people
have their ways,
and bad people have theirs.
Tell me,
did somebody mess with you?
I'll go find some thugs right now
to teach him a lesson.
I... I'm out of water.
Go get me a glass of water.
You got it.
Here's your water.
Where's the boss?
Don't tell me
she went off to tear that scumbag apart?
Oh no.
Boss Bai!
To the abandoned building east of the city, hurry!